lee yon e
kim yong gwan
and also Park Yoon Woo
poton kama ice
all names and events are fictitious
any coincidences are random
drug use is a crime
which entails the destruction of personality
and also negatively affects your 7 and the environment
dear
아 봐 봐
아
아아
dear that gin
favorite
that gin
dear
don't close your eyes
justice has triumphed
from now on
your life will become unbearable just like mine
call an ambulance quickly
Tutjin dear
favorite
no need everything is fine
be patient a little
everything will be fine
Dad's feeling bad here
happy street
house 55 no
come quickly
don't need that gin dad
dear no need
don't close your eyes
dear
dad
please don't
no need
daddy
dad
dear dad
episode twelve
pactojin
아
dear
pak to gin
detective pak pohi
and then the gin is dead
Park To Jin Da Husband Kang In Soo
they were killed by chant haegu
he's on the run now
how can this
that's why I ask
for you to tell everything
otherwise you will rot in prison
thank you
come on
you canensu
you have been arrested for distribution of controlled substances
you have the right to remain silent
whatever you say
can and will be used against you in court
you understand your rights
mom
into the car
on the morning of the 4th, Chan Haegu had an accident near Seoul
Traces of gunfire were found at the scene
upon application
chan haegu he met with informants
but he was attacked
that same night Kang Insu was spotted
on the highway near the scene of the accident and attack
then you both were together with chan haegu
you were all selling mint right
evidence
who is this
sua
you should eat
juju how could she
how could mom
don't cry stop
well
you look so much like your dad
what's the difference
the important thing is that you both were involved in the use of prohibited substances
the deadline will be long
chand hogu tried to kill us
he shot and threatened us
this lady just wanted to escape
a car hit a man
come quickly
we even called an ambulance for him
where did your sales start?
I proposed to her
no you think
the police will believe the nonsense about the suddenly found bag
I offered her to earn money for her husband’s treatment
somehow she wanted to jump off
but I intimidated her
what don't you try to make excuses for?
I won't I can't do it anymore
I don't care about your wishes
but don't you dare stand in my way
let you start this
but I'll finish, you already know
that Taegu was an informant for the phantom and received money from them
the stitcher almost burned him
so he got rid of them and began to threaten us
taegu even killed dong hyuk
he doubled the amount of entsu
get on with it
and I made this lady pay hag
you explained everything to me
then you still believe me
this money then went to me
she also offered to give up together
almost on my knees
what a brainless woman
hubby died
stop it
you will show off until the end of your days and you will not see your daughter
it's her own fault
how are you
how can you
please sit down
yes, have a seat
calm down and sit down
I had to contact this fool
you'll cut my sentence for cooperation
December 8th meeting with investors of Tuin Group
December 8
chant haegu even you closed from that country
and we can’t find this elusive connecting rod
where does this chant haegu hang out?
damn if we don't find him
he can leave the country anyway
so he will get away unpunished
I'll definitely find him, oh my god
how are your fingers
what the doctor says everything has grown together
it doesn't matter of course
it's important you're an artist, I delivered
your product yes
it's because of him
my dad died
I can't forgive
neither you nor myself
no tsua
this is
it's not your fault
it's all because of me dear
I lost everyone I loved
big
I don't want to see you
I came to say this in person
sua sua
daughter
sua
dear sua
kang insoo what's wrong with you
pull yourself together insu
come to your senses
kang insoo wake up
this happened a week after my transfer
parents caught
sold a child for illegal substances
then I was shocked
but later I got used to it
what are you getting at
your story about ikan insu coercion
I almost believed it
but now I understand
you're covering up for insu
trying to save her
what if I dig further
you owe me
that's why I'm giving you a chance
need to lure out Chant Haegu
by any means
Kanens is told the same thing
emphasis in the investigation will be placed
depending on your cooperation
the police received the right to search
Jang Haegu's arrest
accused of murder and distribution of illegal substances
December 6 Jang Haegu
has already been detained
by the police in connection with allegations of corruption
and false denunciation of a colleague
but the suspect managed to escape
at the time of his transfer to the main police station
police released a photo of a wanted man
and requests to immediately contact the authorities
if found
motel desire
one o'clock in the morning on the 11th
white cargo ship in the port of Mansan okay
dance dance
like on a carousel
is that possible?
the main department won't like it
if they interfere
captain chen
we won't catch taegu
it was our business
we have to figure it out ourselves
if anything happens I will take responsibility
kyondo
you've changed
the truth is finally
if we miss him again
we will be thrown out of the police force
dad dad save dad
daddy
want to save your son
come now
find out the place
where is myeongyo
give me back my son
he's with his mom
I'm sorry mingu
go
he's leaving today
에
Tahogu drop your weapon
chand haegu hangs around the area
where his son lives and studies
trying to track him down
he understands he is being watched
can you really lure him out?
by any means
drop the gun
no need
kanintsu don't come near him
people like you
can't be trusted
you won't see children anymore mengio
you
you'll rot behind bars
don't get close to insu
kang insoo
captain chan drop your weapon
everyone stand
he retreats to the exit
아진짜아
아
open
damn
call her an ambulance
and you're still a monster
아
아아
xêr xêr
으으
으
으아슈슈슈슈슈슈슈아
insu you're safe
damn
infection
아
아씨
지옥
보시지
no
we need to call the rescuers
they will examine the curse
call ours
look at her
blue eyes
hello
this is for you
answer me once
please read my letter
beloved daughter
you are the most precious thing
what do I have
how are you doing
Most of all I want to go out and hug my beloved daughter a year later
hi dear
civil affairs department
and you managed quickly
I'm even a little angry
don't look like that
I don't regret anything and I'm not offended
I made a lot of money
dump all the work on you
you really don't regret it
you had things to do while you were free
actually
I wanted to do
something for you
without unnecessary thoughts and calculations
you still have someone to protect
sua let's run to her
it will be strange
if you start crying
still
didn't see through me
I would brainlessly sacrifice myself
Tuen's plans
groups to create an industrial complex with the participation
artificial intelligence
good afternoon, I'm the executive director of kan hverim
at the last shareholders meeting
industrial complex project with participation
artificial intelligence
was a hot topic
to suit the topic being discussed
we have prepared a video featuring my please
project for 1,100,000,000,000 won
this is our future
for your attention
in the city of Insan
Apparently I'm not the only one nervous
this is a project of the future
where artificial intelligence will work autonomously
researching and inventing new technologies
for the benefit of the whole society
mint it's no yes
that's what he's getting off of
not bad how much does it cost
sniff sniff
detain them
Secretary Kim Baldezh
turn it off kancherim
look here
this is a real video
would you like to comment on this?
please comment on the situation
the video is not fabricated
tell me what you think in the video
really you
when was this
who is with you
what kind of mint are you talking about?
where did this video come from
please say something
you use illegal substances
how long ago did this start
we can consider the option
in which you provide a list of all clients
have you heard anything about a fisherman
department for combating prohibited substances
has been following him for several years now
he's a middleman, I'll reveal a big fish for you
consider your proposal
너 왜 그냥 비가 내가 왔을 때
휴가 소리쳐
the video is not fabricated
please tell the truth
tell me you really use illegal substances
give your comment
what drugs do you use
I don't know how you got out
but the floor you are low
penetration in a burglary
addiction to substances and creation of a deepfake
confess and I will spare you
and if not then you're screwed
maybe your family too
at your daddy's
5 projects due next month
oh how much will you lose
if you delay the delivery for another week
bankrupting such a small company is a piece of cake
just like the good old days
who framed me
killing my friend 10 years ago
it was an accident
very sad
but chance is true
your jamb made everyone else unhappy
oh so vindictive
and you're so forgetful
I have to do with this, at least I took proper revenge
drugs
I'm embarrassed to even talk about it
to frame our
the company needed to be pumped up, not me
and my grandfather
shareholders will not rush to sell shares due to misconduct
some executive director
you understand after your stupid video
the share price only dropped by a couple hundred fool
complete waste of time
I went with the rest
you'll figure it out yourself
you've always been like this
incorrigible optimist
don't be afraid of retribution
for any crime
do you think my revenge is over?
I just threw a match
Whoa 4th generation abuses substances
news that will spread
like a forest fire
were high at the party
but then something happened
nothing like that
ate a couple of sweets
but someone
Well, you understand, the police arrived and wanted to tie everyone up
everyone is tied up
only his luck was on my side
will not disappear but what if after a fire
will disappear again
forgotten past
in connection with the probable communion
Kanghwa Rima on the case of the death of a teenager at a party
police may reopen investigation
it is reported that the president of the company is Kangunam
was also involved in falsifying evidence
from the scene of the incident
Tuen Group Business Addicts
built on bones down away
down with 7 murderers and a stone coffin, down with
public mood will worsen
and the government will have to intervene
you will not receive any 1000000000000
they will leave you
don't make me laugh
This is a business, everything has already been decided
that was my goal
but even if it doesn’t work out, the main thing doesn’t matter
to make it look like this
like you're done for director
the government is considering canceling funding for the toin project
groups, you were going to take out a loan as collateral
shares will have to be sold at the lowest price
-30% from the price of the previous day
in 3 days the share price will drop to 10,000
you wanted this
so that you burn out big time
to start a real fire
you need to be patient
the government has begun a review of project support
sold by Tuen Holdings
funding is expected to be canceled for many
many people are concerned about this
Canceling funding will only worsen the current situation
Tuen Group
this 30% will change everything
if at least half a percent is not enough
the controlling shareholder of your wonderful company will change
what do you think
who has this half a percent
freak
I'll kill you
such a creature
well
beg me who knows
maybe you'll have pity
please, I need to talk to my grandfather
but my calls
he doesn't answer
I'll fix everything
just don't leave me
public opinion is riveted on us
we just can't
that's a creature
decided to ditch me
shut up and give the phone to grandpa
now you bastard
hey where did you go
look at yourself
I don't want to be with you
come on here bitch get it
that you consider yourself better
Why am I hanging around with you here?
and you humiliate me
trash
here you go
stop pretending
get up, stand up
grandpa is herself
forgive me grandpa please
have mercy on me grandpa
grandfather
kan hverim located
under investigation for drug use
was arrested for manslaughter
the victim was his girlfriend
famous blogger with more than two hundred 1000 fans
police have also reopened their investigation into the death
teenager died on a giant
10 years ago, the opening of evidence in this case
the chairman of the kangunam is accused
he held a conference
to refute suspicions
and state your version of what happened
I can definitely say
that this matter concerns only the director of Kanherim
accusations against me regarding
closing evidence
cases ten years ago are absolutely groundless
I promise to provide full cooperation to the investigation
so that the case is investigated properly
Toen Holdings found itself at the center of a scandal
share price plummets
along with which investors' fears are growing
everyone is guessing
How negative will this incident be?
and how much the shares will fall
toen group motel miss
I told you I wouldn't sacrifice anything
I came to see you
but there was no one at home
you live here again
yes
how are you
met
with family
yeah, you're still the same
I immediately went to give it to you
thank you thanks to you I was able to take revenge
this is money from the sale of shares
it turned out a lot
I give it back with interest
kakxua
saw her
I can help with something
I'll do anything
let's go fast
Why are you just running?
sua are you safe
ensu run
you will show off until the end of your days and you will not see your daughter
it's her own fault
chant haegu was never found
if you suddenly want
I don't need help
you've done enough really
there was no need to trade
but I'm lucky
that you were my partner
live happily legen
forget about daegu and me
about everything we've done
legen
be happy
ok
I'll be happy
so you don't worry
so you too
be happy
so that I don't worry yes
see you later
forget about haegu already
it's been a whole year already
for the last time
last week you said the same thing
hello yes that's right
what's true
they say they found daegu's body
yes we will now
I'm sorry
that I deceived you
I thought to myself
not so bad
when I did this to you
really sorry doesn't matter I was
same criminal
how are you doing?
I like foster family
I can relax and sleep
and mom's boyfriend doesn't bother me
by the way
jenha's parents did not divorce and moved to the village
that's how it is with you and mom
don't be mad at her
I understand your mother
she just wanted
to make you feel better
은수
when did it come out
the other day
thank you for taking sua with you
soon I will find a home
and I am now sua's legal guardian
your brother her brothers refused
sua wants to be with me
you took my husband to the hospital
it was you who reported it
at me
after everything that happened
are you interested in this
did you even consider me a friend?
of course I liked you
I wanted to become like you
but now that's not the case
call before you come yoju
sua doesn't draw anymore
she can't make the bones grow together
but my fingers still hurt
they say it's psychosomatics
no wonder
you looked so confident
even being lonely
that's why I married you
I'll wait, I'll share the pain with you
I will protect you from judgment
the main thing is we will all be together
darling I lost everyone
whom I loved
more
I don't want to see you
dear
that gin
으흐 으흐
you're great
I'm sorry I didn't believe it right away
sênak
we were waiting for you
welcome back brother
legeno
they took everything
yes then we're leaving
happy street house 55
fast moving cargo transportation service
I grabbed it right away
give it back
there were no insects around the corpse
judging by the remains
their location
death occurred last winter
since you asked
I checked according to dental data
this is chant haegu
autopsy report
he was wearing a bulletproof vest
I don’t see a chest fracture
It's unlikely he died from a bullet
then what is the cause of death
judging by the marks on the right femur, the wound was deep
as a result there was severe bleeding and sepsis developed
It's hard to tell from the bones
hoped to drag it to the next world
so stubborn but everything is even
oblo gone fools
bite the scum
아
Mingio
I won
it's true
will you come with me
Do you think she wouldn't have gotten this far without me?
if she came in sooner or later she would kill someone
for sure
the reason is not important
stepping on this path
there's no turning back
that's life
you and I disagree
we are the same
to today's news
just recently on the mountain
suo skeletal human remains were discovered
according to law enforcement agencies
the remains belonged to police captain Chang Haegu
Hanzali Gretel
Gret or pushed the witch from behind
that she suddenly found herself in the oven
are you seriously sorry
look it right
I worked in a massage parlor
you're in good hands
ok
I want to go to the toilet
damn
hey khvirin
Why did you lie down on the floor?
what the hell
call the warden
come here quickly
the witch screamed
and died in the fire
and the brother and sister took her treasure
and they lived happily ever after
conditions are good
you can sign well
where is the contract from the contractor?
he's definitely in my office
in front of the safe is good
I'll bring it
and you continue
thank you
however
were they happy
construction company
ten holdings
agreement between Lisunsu and Kangunam
what are you doing
father
what is this
why are you
entered into an agreement with Tuen
joint construction for non-disclosure of information
what does this mean
0 2/1011
this is when a friend of the legion died
what do you have there
if you thought
that it's my fault
how are you not embarrassed?
this is an offer from Tuen
father
did you really know
that he was set up
that's not true
say no
legion
you know tell me
that I'm wrong
I couldn't do otherwise
the company was on the verge of bankruptcy
we couldn't go to the bottom because of you
this is the best I could do
selling me is the best
it's all in the past
there's no point in blaming me
sense
do you even know how I lived
I thought if I fixed everything
if I take revenge tuen
you will believe that I am innocent
even when it was so hard
that I wanted to die
I held on just for this
there's no point in blaming
I forced you
you got yourself into this
why did you go to that party
why did you set me up and all your 7 why did you pull me to the bottom
father what
oh you brat
you just left me
but I didn’t know and what a fool I am
kill me come on
경현
wait
legen
keep
yes thank you
you said 180
say thank you for that too
you have a criminal record
If you don't like it, leave
did the children live happily?
killing the witch
to my beloved daughter sua sua
while I'm writing this letter
Snow is falling quietly outside the window
you really love winter
you always ran out
go outside look at 1 snow
I don't know where to start
when your father got sick
I found a bag with substances on the balcony
no, I doubted it for a long time
but driven by the desire to protect 7
decided to do it
something had to be done
I have no right to forgiveness
you can never forgive me
but forgive yourself
sua
don't give up on your dreams
I hope you are more
you'll never lose anything
sua you always
will you be my daughter
don't forget that I always think about you
you are not 1
I will always be
love you and always wait
are you blind or what?
hey oh sorry
win tower
I'm tired of living here
crazy
crossing the line once
can they
do differently
next time
daughter
translated voiced by mobile television studio
commissioned by the online cinema IVI in 2025